One of the things
I would say is
that you there are
super intelligences today and
they're basically large corporations
right They're smarter than
any human can be
at you the problem
of you shipping commerce
at the lowest possible
cost or making solar
panels at the lowest
possible cost or launching
rockets at the lowest
possible cost And so
there's really high returns
to intelligence in this
area which I incentivizes
us to kind
of build the right
thing It's also you
I think it's a
business that is more
stable than consumer We
don't need you know
we don't need ads
don't need you
know large numbers of
free users can just
very directly create value
right There aren't all
these weird externalities of
like you're prioritizing engagement
you're prioritizing these other
things you're all this
slop We just make
stuff that people can
use